Done already. Let's go to the solution. In the menu layout file for the main
activity, called main.xml, we add another menu item
that will always be in the overflow menu.
We also define the string in the strings.xml file. The menu will be inflated in
the main activity class, so we can handle
the map menu item being inflated. By calling
helper method called open preferred location in
map. The helper method reads the users
preferred location from shared preferences. Then we
create a view intent, indicating it's location
in the data URI. The format of the data URI was from the documentation
page on common intents. Where you can append a postal code as a query parameter.
Finally, we start an activity with [SOUND] this intent. Note
that we only start the activity, if the activity resolves successfully.